BGM
Hallo! Ste. 24's Mariaki Makino and Kurumi Takase of Beyones Ame
Kurumi Takase from Morikawa Umi of Beyond's Rain.
This time, we'll be talking with these two, so please bear with us until the end.
The day after tomorrow, February 2, is Mariami Makino's 23rd birthday!
Thank you very much!
I know it's early, but happy birthday!
Thank you very much.
I'm 23 years old, which means that I've grown up a little this year.
I think I'm already an adult, but I want to be more mature.
I would like to be more mature, and I would also like to value my individuality.
Also, I will do my best to improve my dancing.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you very much.
Actually, I would like to work with Ms. Makino as an MC.
I wrote and submitted the questionnaire for Halostei.
You just said that you value individuality, right?
I've been thinking lately that there aren't many people as unique as you.
If I may say so without fear of misinterpretation, Makino-san is very strange, isn't he?
But that's what makes him so attractive as a person.
Together...
During the time when I couldn't do concerts with her, I was watching Morning Musume's solo concerts, and I kept thinking about her.
And then, little by little, we started to have more opportunities to work together.
When I was asked who I wanted to MC with, the first person that came to mind was Makino-san.
I'm so happy!
I'm very happy to be able to MC with you this time.
Thank you very much.
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 of us is now underway!
Tourki Factory Beyones!
Yes, sir.
Morning Musume。24 is touring as the same team A
How do you like it this time?
Well...
It feels more like a Hello Project concert.
That's for sure.
It's like the Hello Project concert that we used to have before the Corona disaster.
The music exchange and shuffle units that we used to have before the Corona disaster...
I feel like it's coming back.
It's really
I'm really enjoying it.
I think so too.
Not completely, but...
Yes.
The three groups have restored the cheering section.
It's back.
I feel nostalgic, but there are members who have not experienced the cheering seats yet, so I think it's a little fresh.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Please take a look.
Here you go.
Thank you very much for watching!
Not in this world! Members with a tremble in their hearts
Mangaland by the Mouth
No! I'm shaking.
Skim skim skim skim skim
High tension
I'm up for the challenge!
High tension!
If he's nice to me, I'll be extra nice.
What's going to happen to my love life?
I'll never meet someone I'll never feel tired I'll never feel tired I'll never feel tired I'll never feel tired
Sweety dance, Tromas show Mona Romas
What's going to happen to your love life?
Leave it to me, life is full of surprises
No!
I can't be pitied
Scare, scare, scare, scare me
Oh, oh, oh
Oh oh oh
Wow!
Oh oh oh oh
Let's jump
Oh oh oh
Wow wow oh oh oh
Rockin'
I wonder if it's in your nature to tent
It's like I'm still stuck in this tent with you
But I try to forgive myself for everything
I can't love myself I want to be loved I want to love myself
I want to be loved, I want to be loved, I want to be loved, I want to be loved...
I can't turn my back on my skin
Wow, wow, wow, wow, I can't stand it anymore
So what?
My life, my life, my life, don't make me look at it again and again
So no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bring it Bring it Bring it
What's that? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, don't lift up your heart
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no. I'm on Blade Reef.
Skiddy Skiddy Skiddy Skiddy Skiddy
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Jump up and down
Charlene Aus
My name is Takamora Oshino of Tsubaki Factory. As I have just announced, I, Takamora Oshino, will graduate from Tsubaki Factory and Hello Project
Tsubaki Factory and Hello Project. I decided to graduate around the time of last year's spring tour, but during this spring tour, I felt that many of the members' personalities were coming out.
I felt that the members' personalities were coming out and I felt that each member was very reliable.
I was able to make the decision to graduate from Hello Project. I love Hello Project and that feeling has never changed.
I am very grateful to the people around me, and I hope to repay them with my performance.
I would like to continue to support Takamora Oshino in the future.
I would like to continue to do my best, so please continue to support Takamora Oshino and Tsubaki Factory.
With Mariya Makino of Morning Musume 24,
I am Marisai Makino of Morning Musume 24 and Kurumi Takase of Morikawa Umi of Beyond's Rain, and I am a member of Halo! Ste.
From here, we would like to talk a little about each other.
Yes, I'm going to ask you a few questions.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly and at a good tempo.
Yes, I will do my best.
Please do.
Kurumi is a certified vegetable sommelier.
Yes, I am.
What vegetable would you like to actively consume this time of year?
Spinach.
You are trying various hair arrangements on this tour.
What is your favorite at the moment?
My hair style is inspired by Amu Hinamori, who is a character in the work "Guardian Character.
Kurumi-chan, the future ambassador of Tochigi.
What do you recommend in Tochigi Prefecture this season?
Strawberries, of course.
Tell us a secret that has yet to be revealed to the world.
I'm actually into ramen by myself these days.
Oh, that's nice.
BEYONES made its major label debut this year.
It's our 5th anniversary. What kind of year do you want this milestone to be?
I want it to be a year of expanding possibilities.
It's more than cool.
Thank you very much.
Wow, you know, there were a lot of things that caught my attention.
Yes.
Hair arrangement.
Do you change your hair arrangement every time?
I do a different hairstyle every time, so far.
Oh.
Yes, there are some cute outfits and some cool outfits.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
Yes, I tried to experiment a little bit, and I tried not to set my possibilities or image in stone.
Yes.
This year.
So I've been doing various hairstyles, and as I search for what kind of hairstyles I like, I'd like to try a hairstyle based on an anime character.
I love anime.
So, when I was looking for various kinds of hairstyles, I thought that if I could do Ami Hinokimori's (the main character) hairstyle, even with my current hair length, I would be able to do it.
I thought I could do it with the same length of hair.
I thought I could do it with the same length, so I did it, and I like it.
It's cute. I don't arrange my hair much.
I don't arrange my hair much.
I'm jealous.
No, no.
There's one more thing that's been bothering me. It's a secret that hasn't come out yet.
Yes.
One man's ramen.
Ramen for one.
What do you recommend?
I like ramen that is very rich.
Wow.
You can go to a really rich tonkotsu ramen place all by yourself.
Iken.
I don't have an Iken yet.
I've never been there.
There are a lot of traditions in Yeken.
That's right. I haven't included that kind of thing either.
I'm planning to go there after I learn it properly.
But you like tonkotsu ramen, right?
Yes, that's right.
I started eating ramen by myself.
I also look up various ramen shops on social networking sites.
Oh.
There's a ramen shop like this near the work site today.
I go there an hour early, eat alone, and then go to work.
You are fully satisfied, aren't you?
Questions for Makina-san will come after the VTR.
Hallo! Ste.
Hello! Ste.
I would like to ask a question to Ms. Makina next!
Yes! Dokidoki!
Here we go!
Tomorrow is the first day of professional baseball camp! What are the highlights of this season for you, Maria Makino?
Creed!
Oh! I'm not blinkered!
Next, Ms. Makino is good at calligraphy, so what word did she choose for the first calligraphy of the year?
Kujiku!
What are you personally looking forward to in 2024?
Live solo tour
What do you recommend to Kurumi Takase, who wants to watch baseball this year?
Watch the live broadcasts.
One month has passed since Morning Musume。 24 changed.
What do you think has changed since you became 24?
When I say "Morning Musume。24," the tension of 24 rises.
Yes, thank you very much.
I understand very well.
When we are touring together and we do a lineup at the end of the tour, you know?
When they call out the name "Morning Musume。24," all the fans say "24.
It was so funny that I kept saying "24" behind their backs.
The year after the name has been added since 14, so it's been 10 years.
So I remember that when I was 14, I had just joined the company and my senpai called me 14, so I can understand how they feel.
I see.
And you mentioned baseball a little bit.
Yes, I did.
I wanted to go see a live baseball game at least once this year.
Yes.
Even a live broadcast would be fun.
But do you know the rules of baseball?
I only have a rough idea.
That's why I thought it would be better to start from the beginning.
The live broadcast shows the players you pay attention to, or...
I see.
With a live commentator and a play-by-play commentator, it's easier to see what the play is about, and they can explain it in detail.
It's hard to understand what's going on from the live broadcast.
So if I watch everything, I can understand what I'm thinking about.
I see.
That's what I was going to recommend.
Please watch the live broadcast and learn from it.
Okay.
Then, if you decide to go to the ballpark next time...
I'll go to the ballpark next time.
I'll be able to say, "Oh, that's the guy I saw on TV.
I see.
That's my way of recommending him.
That's true.
It's more fun to go there with some knowledge than to go there without any knowledge.
It's better that way.
That's true.
It's easier to understand.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, I'm Kimiyami Natsuyaki.
I am Kimiyami Natsuyaki
I am Shiori Nishida of Beyons Subway
I will do my best to complete the project.
I look forward to working with you
Now, what shall we make this time?
Today, pork and cheese millefeuille style
Looks delicious!
Nishida, do you cook?
It is not that I do not cook at all
I do it moderately
I'll try
Seino
Gentle
Looks so delicious!
Where shall we start this time?
Now it's time to make the pork mille-feuille!
We're going to roll it up, but first, let's roll it up.
Mozzarella cheese.
Cut this into about four pieces.
About 4 pieces, about 1 centimeter each.
Or three.
Yes, I understand.
Three more of each.
Three more at a time.
Three at a time.
Keep the basil.
This one... sliced cheese.
Sliced cheese.
Let's cut this one in half once.
Now it's time to roll them up.
This one is big.
Let's go this way.
If you keep rolling it this way, it'll get thicker.
It's better to switch them around.
I see.
If the thin part and the thick part appear...
The way the fire goes in is different.
Yes, that's true.
Yes, it's done.
Spread the salt all over.
Salt all over.
Yes, sir.
From the top
Para para
High power
Shush, shush, shush.
If you make it go all over
Yes, sir.
And now
Flour lightly.
All over like this, too.
Yes.
And mozzarella.
Yes, sir.
Roll up the cheese first.
Sir, is it okay if I roll it up a little bit?
It's okay, just a little bit.
Just a little.
The meat shrinks when it cooks.
Oh, it shrinks.
It shrinks.
Around there.
Around here.
And put the cheese slices here.
It looks so good when you're doing it, doesn't it?
Delicious.
This is delicious.
Wow, okay.
It's pretty big.
It's huge!
Volume
One more layer.
Another layer? More?
That's what I'd like you to do.
But it takes a lot of time to do that.
I see.
I'll give it a try.
It's going to be cool.
It's going to be great.
But... it's hard to heat up.
That's the only thing.
I'm not trying to shorten the time, but... making it at home...
Make it a little thinner.
I think it's okay to make it a little thinner.
Oh, wow!
Dream
Here it comes!
I'm going to bake it.
A little more than I expected
This is hot!
I think it's going to take a long time.
Of course it will.
But it's going to be great when it's done.
Yes, I'd like to bake it.
Yes, sir.
A teaspoon.
5 cc.
Yes, that's right.
And the sides are hard to bake.
So I'm going to grill the sides first.
Okay.
Yo!
Yes!
Is it right?
Yeah, hold on.
Next time I do it this way, there will be oil dripping.
Here, let the teacher do it.
Yes, sir.
With tongs.
That's not fair.
It's a little difficult.
It's better the other way around.
Oh, wow.
Now, by browning the sides.
the cheese won't come out.
Oh!
oh?
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Then let's slowly bake it
On this side.
When you go this way after baking the side...
You have to cook the joint first.
If you don't burn that part...
If you don't, it will peel off.
It's getting a nice brown color.
That's great.
That's good.
Let's start here.
Here we go.
Is this... is this... is this...
Yes, that's it!
Miyamizu Point
Yay!
Put the lid on it
Put the lid on it.
Put the lid on
Steam and roast
Yes, sir.
I'm a volunteer.
It's so big.
It's hard to cook.
That's right.
Put the lid on.
Put a lid on it and let it steam.
Steam it.
Yes, sir.
It may take more than 10 minutes.
It may take about 15 minutes.
Yes, sir.
Steam-baked.
I see.
But you like cooking?
Yes, I do.
You like doing it?
But it takes me a long time.
It takes you a long time?
Yes, I'm still slow at cutting vegetables.
Hmm.
The knife?
The knife.
Yes, that's right.
I'm afraid.
I'm a little afraid.
Do you ever cook for your family?
My mother recently injured her finger.
She was always in charge of cooking for the family, but she couldn't do it anymore, so for a while...
If I don't do it then...
I had to do it myself.
No, I thought I had to do it myself, so I made it.
I had to do it myself, so I made it.
I made it because I had to do it myself
I had to do it myself
What did you make then? A hamburger patty. It was amazing. I was crying as I cut onions and made hamburgers, but they said they wanted hamburgers and asked me to use ground meat.
Let's measure the temperature.
It's already bursting.
It's amazing.
It's nicely browned.
The core should be in the middle of the meat.
Here we go.
Ready?
Stop here.
Oh, it's all right.
It's over 60 degrees.
There's a limit of how long it takes to reach 63 degrees, but...
But the basic rule is to make sure it's above 60 degrees.
You're absolutely fine.
Good, good, good.
Okay, okay. I'm almost done.
At the end, we'll sprinkle basil on top.
Cut the basil one slice at a time.
And the basil as close to the edge as possible.
If you do it at the beginning, it will turn black.
That's about right.
Take this off and make it a little smaller here.
I think that's good.
Here we go.
Cut it right here, right in the middle
Yes, it's okay, it'll be crushed
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
Yes, like this, horizontally
Yes, yes
Oh!
And basil.
A little olive oil before putting it on the basil
Like drawing a picture all at once.
That's good.
And basil.
Yes. - This one's expensive, too.
It's good, isn't it?
Beautiful!
Beautiful.
It's done!
See you!
Pork and cheese millefeu style is ready!
What do you think? Look at how it looks! It's so hearty!
It's so delicious and looks like it's the star of the show!
I feel like my stomach is about to rumble right before my eyes! Let's have them eat it now!
Bon appétit!
Hmmm...
What do you think?
Here it comes! Asato!
Asato!
It's delicious.
I'm so glad!
You can taste the cheese and the crispy texture of the sauce.
The sauce is really smooth and very tasty!
It was a great success.
How was your experience in Hello Kids?
It was a lot of fun. This was my second time to participate in Hello Kids, and I was praised for being a little better with the knife than I was then.
Thank you very much!
Please come visit Hello Kids again!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much! 24's Mariaki Makino and
Beyondz Ame no Mori Kawakai Naosho Kurumi
Halo! Ste. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11
From here is a new project!
Project Project No.1
We are going to introduce a new project called "Chotto No.1". Project members
Project members on a little bit of a theme.
We will announce who is the No.1 in the ranking form!
Here it is!
The theme this time is
Which member do you think is the most stoic?
I'd like to say...
Yes
Morning Musume。 24?
Well, let's see...
Sakura Oda.
I think singing is all about pursuit and pursuit.
She is very particular about the sound and even a little bit particular about it.
and she communicates it to the members.
I think she's stoic in that way.
Kurumi
With Beyondz, it's a bit of a choice between the two.
Yeah.
You mean Mano-chan?
Yes.
Or Shin Maeda?
Oh...
I guess.
Yeah, yeah.
They're both very straight-laced.
Yes, they are.
I feel that they put their all into everything they do.
So...
I think one of them is in the list.
Let's take a look at the ranking.
First of all, let's look at No. 3.
The comments from the voting members are
Yes.
I admire the way she always gives her all in everything she does.
This is Kanami Ishiguri.
Yes, I do.
One more thing, I think you are a professional in body building and performance.
Yes.
This is Ruru from Damba.
So, the members who are the most stoic are...
The third place goes to Mariya Makino of Morning Musume。 24, who got a whopping 6 votes!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
I know the word "Kokuhata Kami" which is also Sho Nakata's favorite word, and I know it very well.
The spirit to overcome oneself.
I know that word very well.
I want to keep that as my goal from now on.
Now, let's go to the next show!
Let's go to Halostei!
The second place goes to Ruri Hiromoto, who was voted as the best because she is always studying with us at rehearsals and during breaks at the Dance Academy.
Ruri Hiromoto from Dance Academy.
And from Horoka Kobayashi, who I've been watching closely and I'm amazed at how she always manages her body shape and diet.
That means... I'm so excited!
The second most stoic member of the group, with eight votes, is Michiyo Hirai of Beyonce's Seasonings.
As Honoka Kobayashi said in her comment, she doesn't use the word "diet" very often, but rather "weight loss.
She is like an athlete, but she has to decide what she wants to eat every day, and she does her best not to eat anything other than what she has decided to eat.
She even calculates the calories and does things that you wouldn't normally do, like deciding on a month's worth of food ahead of time and following that plan.
I think it's really cool that she doesn't compromise on her performance, which is probably why she is able to express her opinions to her seniors.
It's really cool.
Now, the first place winner will be announced after the VTR.
Brizara!
First place will be announced after the VTR.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The monthly line of companies and roadside inns Oh No!
Commuting time and full-tuition Expanding city Oh No! Where is the paradise?
Hating someone doesn't make you happy or strong
Then, now love love love rain
Otorogo happy dance, proper happy dance
I can hear more and more happy dancing
This is the happy dance This is the coca so pan
I'll fly in space, pang pang pang pang, I wanna do the exit, pang pang pang pang, I wanna do the exit
I want to love you so much I want to love you so much I want to love you so much I want to love you so much
Because it's not working Happy Song
I'm gonna get married on weekends and holidays
Say Ho!
Say Ho! The original You
It's everyone's first time in life
I hope you make the meaning of life
Here, in your hand now
Happy night with you tonight
Happy time echoes Happy time echoes
It's fun. You want to put it out into the universe?
I said it's an eye strike.
Papa Papa Papa Papa Papa Papa Papa Papa
I'm gonna put the kiter on, just so you can have it
I'll melt the galaxy
Happy Song
8888888
888ppppa
Woo Woo
It's a real real world
Oh oh oh oh yeah
Oh oh oh
Lappy Ray tonight, happy night with you
Lappy Ray, Lappy Ray, Lappy Ray
Happy site with us I want to see it from you
You're the fun lappy
I'm leading the way
Pan, pan, pan, pan, pan
Beaten by Akechi
Pan pan pan pan pan pan pan
Upcooked, you look so bright
Ringer, let's stretch it out
Happy Soul
Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이 Sound Hodori
Happy Song
Thanks to you, I can do my best
Morning Musume。 24's Mariaki Makino and
BEYONDZ Rain Forest Shoki Kawakami Naoki Kurumi presents Halo! STE
I'd like to introduce a little bit to all the members of the Halo! Project members were surveyed on a little theme.
Project to find out who is the number one in a ranking format.
This time, the members who are the most stoic are
Third place goes to Mariaki Makino, who received 6 votes!
And the second place goes to Mio Hirae, who got 8 votes.
Who is the member who is the most stoic?
Please take a look at the VTR.
The reason is that I think she is very stoic about her performance.
I have also been taught the rhythm of the music, thankfully.
I can't give advice if you don't put in the effort first.
You have to be stoic to yourself and stoic to your work.
Even when you're walking down the hallway, you always look like you're in rhythm, and that's really cool.
I'm reminded of that, and I love singing, and I'm very stoic, and I think it's cool.
I always think it's cool that they are so stoic.
The member who I think is the most stoic is Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。
I think of her stoicism very much.
It's embarrassing to say this, but I thought, "Wow!
I'm embarrassed to say it, but I thought, "Wow. I am happy to know that you see me that way, but I was also surprised that you see me that way from my belly.
I was very happy that they saw me that way, and if they were inspired by me even a little, then there was some meaning in what I was saying.
I was very happy, and it made me feel that I have to become a senior who matches the impression I have. Thank you all very much.
I don't know.
One thing that I think is unusual is that when I sing a hana uta, if I don't like it, I have to re-sing it or re-sing it until I am satisfied with it.
I teach rhythm very well. If it is ZUNK's song, I have taught myself a lot.
I have taught myself a lot of ZUNK's songs, and I can't say that this is the correct answer.
I have learned a lot of ZUNK's songs, and I know that this is the right answer,
There is no right answer for expression, but for rhythm
I don't have the right answer for expression, but I do have the right answer for rhythm, and I feel that the instruments are in rhythm, but the song is not in rhythm with the instruments.
I sometimes think it's disrespectful to the instrumentalists when I'm singing.
So I pay a lot of attention to the rhythm.
I'm sorry that other people thought I was being nosy, but I'm just saying, "This is how it's done.
I'm sorry that other people think I'm nosy, but when I tell them what I'm trying to do here and ask them to sing it, it's like a song for me.
I think it makes the song sound professional.
I'm hoping that this song will reach the younger generation without losing the idea that this is the kind of song I'm singing while I'm here.
Since it was chosen, I will continue to do my best to keep that impression, so please watch over me.
I'm satisfied with the first place.
Actually, I voted for Oda-san, too.
I was wondering if there are many members who got advice from you about their singing.
Even during the concert, he told me to calm down and sing more calmly, and even though I was still singing, he still called out to me.
He still called out to me, and so on.
After the concert, I asked Mr. Oda about it and he said, "If you notice it soon, you can call me Nasashi.
After the concert, I also asked Mr. Oda to tell me if he noticed anything.
Even during the concert, I would listen to the members' songs and think about what I should do.
Even in rehearsals, he always tries to make it easier for everyone to listen and sing.
He always does that for me.
I really trust you a lot when it comes to performance and singing.
I have a lot of trust in Mr. Oda when it comes to performance and singing.
During the current tour, he has been helping the younger members who are struggling in terms of singing.
Oda-san was always there to listen to them in detention practice.
Even in the backstage, he would call the struggling singers to come next to him and listen to them all the time.
He would listen to them and give them detailed instructions like, "You're off, you're not right here.
He listened to me as I gave him detailed instructions.
Recently, I've been watching him closely.
I think it's very understandable.
I also received a lot of advice at the Hello! Project concert when I first joined the group.
I want to do my best to become a senior member like that.
Please look forward to the next Hello!
Valentine's Day is coming soon. What kind of chocolate do you like?
With Mariaki Makino of Morning Musume。 24
Project, and Kurumi Takase of "Beyones, Rain Forest, River Sea". Sta", presented by Kurumi Takase of Beyones, Ame no Mori Kawai.
It's almost time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
We are going to hold "Halo! Project 2024 Winter 3 of us is now underway!
Morning Musume。24 BEYONES is in Team A with Tsubaki Factory!
The next performance will be in Fukuoka on February 3!
Please come and join us!
And the BEYONES will be performing on February 4.
Hallo! Music Festival 2024 in Tokyo!
Music Festival 2024 in Tokyo on Feb. 4. Pro trainee unit 24 will be performing at the festival.
Sanrio's event, so the members are very excited!
Please come and join us!
Also, we will be performing at the Theater Girls Club last fall.
The Blu-ray of "Biospy's Missing Attache Case" will be released this spring.
will be released this spring!
Please check it out as well!
Morning Musume。24
23 25th anniversary concert tour
Grad Quarter Century at Nippon Budokan on Blu-ray DVD
February 7, 2012.
Please check it out!
And on March 30 and 31, we will be holding the "2024 by Satomi Satoyama Movement" at Makuhari Messe to think about carbon neutrality.
2024 by Satomi Satoyama Movement will be held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
We are looking forward to seeing what this year's event will be like.
We are looking forward to seeing what this year's event will be like!
Please come and join us!
We are looking forward to seeing you this year!
We are looking forward to seeing you this year! Project is a channel where the members of the Halo! Project members will appear more and more on this channel!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time we're joined by Mariya Makino from Morning Musume。 24 and Kurumi Takase from BEYONDZ Ame no Mori Kawai.
BEYONDZ: Kurumi Takase of Ame no Mori Kawai!
Good bye.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!